flash-game.net 2016-03-06

# Privacy policy by Flash Game

##  Privacy Policy 

  * **1\. Information Collection and Use** Flash Game is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Flash Game collects information from our users at several different points on our website.
  * **2\. Log Files** We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
  * **3\. Sharing** We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
  * **4\. Links** This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we [Flash Game] are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
  * **5\. Tell to friends** If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. Flash Game will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Flash Game stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact Flash Game at INSERT URL to request the removal of this information from their database.
  * **6\. Notification of changes** If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

**Our 100 Most-Searched Flash Games**
